<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>learning on zufrieden.io/</title>
    <link>https://zufrieden.io/tags/learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in learning on zufrieden.io/</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 14:13:56 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zufrieden.io/tags/learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How and why asking for help</title>
      <link>https://zufrieden.io/writing/leadership-how-and-why-asking-for-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 14:13:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zufrieden.io/writing/leadership-how-and-why-asking-for-help/</guid>
      <description>Asking for help is fine We tend to not ask for help. Usually because it transmit the idea of a weak person. It may expose our weakness right. But human being likes to help and saying you need some help is a good honest gesture. Because you can&amp;rsquo;t do everything alone right.
3 reinforcements that helps to get buys-in  Being part of the group is something you have to consider when asking for help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Look for Integrity</title>
      <link>https://zufrieden.io/linking/look_for_integrity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 14:20:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zufrieden.io/linking/look_for_integrity/</guid>
      <description> “You’re looking for three things, generally, in a person,” says Buffett. “Intelligence, energy, and integrity. And if they don’t have the last one, don’t even bother with the first two. I tell them, ‘Everyone here has the intelligence and energy—you wouldn’t be here otherwise. But the integrity is up to you. You weren’t born with it, you can’t learn it in school.”
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My leadership cheatsheet</title>
      <link>https://zufrieden.io/writing/leadership_cheatsheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 13:49:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zufrieden.io/writing/leadership_cheatsheet/</guid>
      <description>Seeking the right role for an Entrepeneur  becoming an observer instead of an active participant in your business Entrepreneurship is really just a fancy word for delegation   &amp;ldquo;My company felt like an unmanned car, slowly swerving into the ditch only to be pulled back — usually by me — at the last second.&amp;rdquo;
  &amp;ldquo;Many CEO’s forget this and get stuck in sales, marketing, product — whatever part of the business they love — while they ignore the bigger picture.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>